- Hey, Pen!
- Huh? What is it?
Well, I was thinking about some stuff,
and I thought of something that
might be a really cool coincidence!
And, what would that be?
I wonder what would happen if you took
the first spoken word of the first episode,
the second spoken word of the second episode,
all the way until the 25th spoken
word of the 25th episode...
- Yeah?
- ...and lined up those words to make a message.
W-what would you get?
I don't know, probably nothing.
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
Announcer:
22 cakes have come and gone,
but none of them are nearly as
magnificent as the Grand Cake.
Bubble:
That is seriously a hideous cake!
Really, Bubble? When did I say you
were allowed to speak?
Never. But let's do Cake at Stake!
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ The points are gone ♪
♪ We are free of them now ♪
♪ But we look on ♪
♪ To the moment that we see ♪
♪ The next slice of cake ♪
♪ A step closer to the prize ♪
♪ Brought on by- ♪
Everyone:
Cake at Stake!
Aw, seriously?!
We're going to release the eliminated contestants.
Leafy:
No! Don't do that!
Why not?
Firey:
You dunno?
After years of seclusion, those...
those creatures have gone INSANE!
Announcer:
Too late.
See? They're perfectly fi-
Ough!
Are you all ready for the æ?
Ae? What's the æ?
I said æ. æ. ææææ.
Well, I guess I'm unable to
pronounce the 'ay sound anymore.
You mean the K sound?
You can't pronounce the K sound!
Whatever, now be 'uiet.
Thanks a lot, Flower.
You've messed up the Announcer!
O'ay, moving on.
The... uhm... pastry, is all of the previous
pastries meshed together.
Oh wow!
Auuuuuuuuugh...
Leafy, stop salivating.
Firey, you too, or you'll destroy yourself.
Ahhhhh... GAH!
Hurry up, already!
So the person who got the most votes,
will get this entire pastry,
along with Dream Island as well.
We got 870 votes, which means
there will be no Season Two.
Aww!
Before we announce the winner of BFDI,
let's see who the eliminated people want to win.
Well, Leafy's killed me, Bubble's killed me,
and Firey's killed me,
so I don't think any of them should win.
But if we absolutely had to choose
one of them, who would it be?
Leafy! Because she's a plant.
Announcer:
Spongy.
Leafy!
Leafy, 'cause Firey's deadly
and Bubble's fun to kill.
Leaveh...
Leafy!
Wow, Pin! You remembered our-
Pin, alliance, remember?
Pin:
Oh yeah.
Of course!
And Needy, you vote for Leafy, too! Right?
Don't call me Needy! But no.
Then who?
Firey!
Announcer:
Teardrop, are you going to vote?
Leafy, and I realize all of the finalists
weigh less than 1/10 of an ounce.
I vote Leafy, definitely not Firey.
Me too!
OMG! Bubble!
Leafy.
Leafy!
Uhh, Bubble.
LEAFY! Leafy! Leafy, I mean Leafy!
[leaves rustle]
Leafy!
Bleh!
Leafy wins by a 15:2 vote.
Yay!
But that doesn't mean you win Dream Island.
Then who wins Dream Island?
Whoever got the most votes from the viewers.
Bubble, I'm sorry, but you only received 228 votes,
so you don't win, but you played a great game.
Announcer:
You were a wonderful 'ontestant.
Oh, do I at least get a prize?
You get one 'ashew.
Bless you!
No, I said 'ashew.
Wow, you must be allergic to something.
'Ashew. 'Ashew. 'Ashew.
Maybe the announcer is allergic to this cashew.
Here, you can have it, Bubble!
YOYLECAKE!
So the winner is either Firey or Leafy.
Firey, y-you're such a great friend.
I'll be happy if either of us win.
Let's show the votes.
What? No drumroll? Why not?
Budget 'uts.
- Uhhh...
- I mean budget downsizings.
So, Firey, you win.
Yeah-hah!
Huhel...
Before I give you Dream Island,
I want to than' the viewers for viewing,
and the voters for voting.
Than's go out to jaysillyboy for voting the first ever vote,
cheryblosen for the last ever vote,
and the 6,814 votes in between.
Hurry up!
Okay, let's go.
First, choose the people who should
be allowed onto the island.
Hmmm...
Choose us!
Yeah, choose us! Choose us!
Okay!
YOYLECAKE!
Needle, you were the only person to vote for me.
I appreciate that.
You can come in, too!
What about us?
Yeah, you can come in too.
Yeah, thanks!
You can pass, you can pass,
you guys can all pass.
Hey, wait, wait, wait! David, I don't know about you.
Aw, seriously?
Okay, go ahead.
Flower, I still think you're a jerk
but you can come in.
Wow, Firey, that's so nice of you!
You'd better let me in, or else!
No! Are you serious? Think of all the
things that you've done!
But that's just it. I've grown closer to you
than anyone you've ever known!
I mean, if there's anyone who should be let
into the island, it should be me!
Y-you're right! Get in there Coiny!
Wow, Firey, tha-that was... that was amazing!
On another note, I can't wait to see Dream Island.
Well, Leafy, I don't think I can let you in.
What!? But you let everybody else in, even Coiny!
Leafy, when you rode my ferris wheel, you said...
Get me outta this thing!
That really hurt me; deep down inside.
You better be joking, Firey!
Leafy, you don't understand!
That ferris wheel, I made it for myself,
but more importantly I made it for you
and you just rejected it.
Firey, I don't believe this!
Leafy, I'm sorry, but now I see the truth.
You are a mean person, and I do not believe
you deserve to be on Dream Island.
Announcer, give me Dream Island!
Ooh, Dream Island is expensive.
Are you able to afford it?
Oh! U-uh, nyuh-huh... Yeah!
Wow! This will help pay for our budget.
That should do it.
Huh- uhh, what is going on? Where is Dream Island?!
We had to sell it because of budget slicings.
- Everyone: Ahhhh!
- David: Aw, seriously?
- Blocky: Did you just say that?
Seriously, Speaker Box. You can't just sell Dream Island!
I did.
What?! Guys, we have to get Dream Island back!
According to my imagination, 99.8% of
all islands are destroyed within 2 hours of being sold.
Yeah, face it, Pen. We're not
getting Dream Island back.
But... 2 years of battling!
Pen, 2 years is nothing.
Get over it already!
Am I really the only person who wants
Dream Island? At all?
I want Dream Island.
Finally! See? Eraser has a brain.
But erasers don't have brains.
I want Dream Island too!
OMG, why don't we just, like, find out who
got Dream Island right now?
Yeah! Hey Announcery, who did you sell Dream Island to?
I 'an't tell you that.
Please!
No,
No.
If you won't tell me, I'm gonna cry, and I cry acid!
Ha, ha. 'lever. I mean 'unning.
I mean 'rafty. I mean-
Hey, where's Leafy?
Firey, don't tell me you rejected
Leafy from Dream Island!
Ahh... Oh my gosh, look! It's a UFO!
I'm not falling for that trick.
Tennis Ball, Match, Snowball, and Woody:
Ahhhhhh!
U-uhm...
Hey guys, I'm back!
H-Hello? Excuse me, where's the celebration?
Flower, I'm tired of this.
Wha-what do you mean?
I mean, I'm tired of your self-centeredness.
I'm tired of the way you act around us.
You know what that means? I'm tired of YOU!
- Gasp! Bubble!
- Flower, your unpopularity is your own fault.
Everyone hates you because we can't
stand how you talk only about yourself!
Okay, if that's the way you want to be, fine.
If you don't want me, I don't want you!
Wait, what?
Oh, Flower, what are you doing?!
Bubble, you should've seen this coming.
Bubble:
F-Flower, you need to calm down!
Bubble, I'm sorry. Oh wait, I'm not.
Oh, and it turns out that that was the
last Bubble Recovery Center. Ever.
Flower, you are an evil person!
If that's how you're gonna treat
others then I think you need punishment.
Firey, you do not kill a flower!
How does that feel?
So...
OMG, we can play Spongy Cake!
Uh, I don't know what that is,
but it sounds pretty dumb.
Aren't any of you concerned about the fact
that we're in an Unidentified Flying Object?
Okay, TB, take a chill pill.
First off, it isn't unidentified.
What?
Match is right. It says the
"Announcer Transportation Device."
And second, it's not flying.
What do you mean? Of course it is!
Not anymore.
Everyone:
Ahhhhh!
Teardrop, help me find out who has Dream Island!
- Can I?
- Sure!
- I'll help as well.
- So where do we start?
Let's ask Leafy. She's on the
other side of the gate.
Leafy, do you have Dream Island?
No?
Firey really needs that island. He deserves it!
Leafy:
I have to disagree with that.
The way he acted was just...
...Wonderful!
Bul-
Match, flip the switch back! Start flying again!
I can't! It's like a one-way lever or something!
There's all the other Announcers!
No way.
Finally! No more vomit!
Bleh!
Ice Cube? Uh, not worth it.
Flower! You've got to stop!
Yeah, Flower, end this immediately!
Wow, that's the first time you two have ever
agreed without arguing... I think.
Gah! Bleh...
Has Flower finally stopped her evil doings?
Nope!
I really don't know why Firey would do that.
It seems he turned from a nice caring friend into jerk!
A hideous, unloving jerk with no feelings at all!
Leafy, I know you're upset, but that
doesn't mean you have to call him names!
Maybe we can talk about it?
You know, to soothe your feelings!
Sorry, Pin, I don't want to talk right now.
I know Firey excluded you from Dream Island,
but don't worry about it too much!
- Especially because-
- I know,
especially because Firey never
received Dream Island at all.
Wait, how do you know that?
Urh, I heard him talking through the wall.
But isn't that wall soundproof?
I think I know whats going on.
You BOUGHT Dream Island, didn't you?
That's how you know everything!
This is all your fault, isn't it? Firey rejected you,
you wanted revenge!
Isn't that what happened? Admit that's what happened,
Leafy! Admit it already!
Eraser:
Guys, do you see that? She's turning evil!
Ice Cube:
Wha?
Pin:
What? That's crazy!
I think it's time to see what's really going on
inside this so-called Leafy!
Yeah!
Eraser:
Football?!
I didn't mean that literally!
[Everyone protesting]
Here goes that last and most
important recovery center!
I think my work here is done!
Don't you realize what you just did?!
All the damage you caused?!
Now if anyone dies, they'll be gone FOREVER!
And that's what I want!
Bubble, you were nice to me
sometimes but not enough times,
and to be honest I'm not
sad to see you go.
Everyone:
Gasp!
Who's next?
Flower, calm down!
Do you really want to do this?!
Yes, of course I want to do this! That's why I-
What is going on?
Hey guys! OMG, I'm alive!
Yeah, but you killed someone else
under your massive machine.
Oh my gosh, is it Pencil?
It better not be Pencil!
It's Flower.
Well that's good then!
Tennis Ball, where's Woody?
- He died.
- Yeah, we did crash pretty hard.
No, he died long before we landed.
Tennis Ball:
His fear of the color grey gave him a heart attack.
We're glad you managed to recover the
funds we've lost during this campaign.
It's proven unsuccessful,
and now it's time to come home.
- But what about-
- It's okay, we can always return.
Hey peoples! A meteorite just hit Rocky,
so he can't barf anymore.
Wow, that's amazing!
Where's Leafy? I want to apologize for excluding her!
She didn't deserve to be treated that way.
Well, it turns out that Leafy isn't
such a nice person after all.
Golf Ball:
Leafy was the one who bought Dream
Island so none of us could have it.
Everyone:
Gasp!
I think Leafy deserves the death penalty!
Everyone:
Yeah!
I found Flower's Announcer Crusher!
I'm pretty sure it will do the job!
Wow! Good job, Pencil!
Any last words, Leafy?
Yeah, I-
Everyone:
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill-
Hey, like, what's that thing over there?
Gasp!
What are you doing? Get your
hands off of me you jerk!
Leafy, Leafy! Leafy, I'm sorry for what I did.
I realized that what I wanted most wasn't Dream Island.
It's you, your friendship.
I just want you to know that I'm tired of all this
turmoil that's going on, all these conflicts and stuff.
And I'd rather spend my time with you,
whether it's on Dream Island or not.
Really? You mean it?
Hurry up! We have to get back to the execution!
♪ Uhhh-ahhhhhhh! ♪
♪ Smaller cap equals less plastic, plastic! ♪
♪ Tong Yang Hi! ♪
♪ I am a banana, yeah! ♪
♪ Ahhhhhhhhhhh! ♪
♪ Warning: A Cap is small part and poses
as a choking hazard particularly for children, yeah! ♪
♪ NEVER SAY NEVER! ♪
♪ Ahhhhhhhhhhh! ♪
♪ Mmmmm... ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
Hey, Match!
Wouldn't it be weird if the very first and
very last spoken words of BFDI were the same?
Yeah!